tesco.com.my 2017-12-21

# Tesco :: Privacy Policy

Tesco.com.my ("Tesco Website") is owned and operated by Tesco Stores (Malaysia) Sdn. Bhd. ("Tesco"). Tesco is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how Tesco may use information we collect about you and our data processing practices. By using the Tesco Website, you confirm your understanding and consent unconditionally to the terms of this Policy. This Policy applies to users in Malaysia only. 

#### Information we collect about you 

Tesco collects the details provided by you on registration together with information we learn about you from your use of our service and your visits to our Tesco Website. 

We may collect additional information about you when you:

  1. visit the Tesco Website;
  2. register with and buy products or services e.g in-store, online or take part in promotions, competitions, customer surveys and questionnaires;
  3. provide us feedback or contact us eg in writing or call customer services

#### Using your information

Collecting your personal information helps Tesco to better understand what you need from us. We use your information to:

  1. manage and improve the scheme
  2. administer your account and send you your statement and mailings
  3. understand your shopping behaviour in order to develop and improve our products and services
  4. manage promotions, competitions, customer surveys and questionnaires
  5. check and verify your identity

#### Other Tesco products and services

We may share your personal information across the Tesco group so they can provide you with relevant products and services. They may ask you for your Clubcard details and, if so, explain how your information will be used by them. 

#### Marketing and research

Unless you indicate otherwise, we may contact you:

  1. with offers and information about Tesco products or services
  2. with offers and information about partners' products or services
  3. for customer research e.g. to help improve our services

Of course, the choice is entirely yours, but if you say you do not want to receive marketing information from us this will prevent you from receiving great offers or promotions that may be of interest to you. 

#### Cookies

We use a system of classifying the different types of cookies which we use on the Website, or which may be dropped by third parties through our websites. The classification explains more about which cookies we use, why we use them, and the functionality you will lose if you decide you don't want to have them on your device. 

#### What is a cookie? 

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information which are downloaded to your personal computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website. Cookies are then sent back to the originating website on each subsequent visit, or to another website that recognises that cookie. Cookies are useful because they allow a website to recognise a user's device. 

Persistent cookies - these cookies remain on a user's device for the period of time specified in the cookie. They are activated each time that the user visits the website that created that particular cookie. 

Session cookies - these cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. A browser session starts when a user opens the browser window and finishes when they close the browser window. Session cookies are created temporarily. Once you close the browser, all session cookies are deleted. 

Cookies do lots of different jobs, like letting you navigate between pages efficiently, remembering your preferences, and generally improve the user experience. They can also help to ensure that adverts you see online are more relevant to you and your interests. 

#### Cookies used on the Website

A list of all the cookies used on the Website by category is set out below. 

#### Strictly necessary cookies 

#### These cookies enable services you have specifically asked for.

These cookies are essential in order to enable you to move around the Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the Website. Without these cookies services you have asked for, like shopping baskets or e-billing, cannot be provided. 

#### Performance cookies 

#### These cookies collect anonymous information on the pages visited. 

These cookies collect information about how visitors use the Website, for instance which pages visitors go to most often, and if they get error messages from web pages. These cookies don't collect information that identifies a visitor. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous. It is only used to improve how the Website works. 

#### Functionality cookies 

#### These cookies remember choices you make to improve your experience. 

These cookies allow the Website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more personal features. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you have asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect may be anonymised and they cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. 

#### Targeting or advertising cookies 

#### These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. 

These cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with our permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organisations such as advertisers. Quite often targeting or advertising cookies will be linked to site functionality provided by the other organisation.

#### Using browser settings to manage cookies 

The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether. You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-on's settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer. 

However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of the Website's essential features, we recommend you leave them turned on. For example, if you block or otherwise reject cookies you will not be able to add items to your Shopping Basket, proceed to Checkout, or use any of our products and services that require you to Sign in. If you leave cookies turned on, remember to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

#### Disclosures and transfer of your information 

We will never disclose your information to anyone outside the Tesco Group (within or outside Malaysia) except where we have your consent; where we are required or permitted to do so by law; to other companies who provide a service to us; or any successors in title to our business. 

#### Accessing your information

To obtain a copy of the information we hold about you, please contact our Clubcard Helpline on 1 300 13 1313. Please confirm your Clubcard number and any details to help us identify and locate your information. If any of the details are incorrect, let us know and we will amend them.

#### Changes to our privacy policy 

This privacy policy replaces all previous versions and is correct as of May 2014. Tesco reserves the right to change the policy at any time. 

#### Contacting us

If you have any queries, please contact us at www.tesco.com.my or call our Clubcard Helpline on 1 300 13 1313.
